CIERRA M. POWELL

161 Crawford Street Biloxi, Ms. 39530 • Cell: 2283241261 • Cierra Powell 1993@gmail.com

Education

Associate of Applied Science : Hotel and Restaurant Management , 2015 MGCCC Jefferson Davis Campus - Gulfport, Mississippi

- Coursework in Hotel Management and Hospitality Management
- Coursework in Restaurant and Hospitality Operations
- Serve Safe certified
- Certified in F&B through the Hotel and Lodging Association in 2013

Skills

- Quick problem solver
- Committed team player
- High energy
- Guest relations professional
- Up-selling capability

- Thrives in fast-paced environment
- Courteous, professional demeanor
- ServSafe certification
- Cash handling expert
- Liquor and smoking laws familiarity

Summary

Highly effective at anticipating and accommodating customer needs. Friendly, punctual and enthusiastic team player.

Hardworking loyal employee who thrives under pressure and goes above and beyond to create unforgettable guest experiences. 6+ years experience in all areas of the FOH and BOH

Expert at multi-tasking and delivering prompt and friendly service to all customers. Maintains a positive attitude and a great sense of humor during peak hours.

Experience

Hostess, 03/2010 to 10/2012

Back Bay Seafood Restaurant - Gulfport, Mississippi

- Greet guest
- Properly seat guest according to server seating chart
- Recorded to go orders and accurately entered into a point of sale system
- Set scheduled party tables up prior to arrival
- Buss tables reset tables
- Use of Point of Sale system

Hostess, 10/2012 to 07/2014

Hook Up Restaurant – Biloxi, Mississippi

- Greet guest
- Properly seat guest according to server seating chart
- Recorded to go orders and accurately entered into a point of sale system
- Set scheduled party tables up prior to arrival
- Buss tables reset tables
- Expedited food and carried to tables on large trays using service legs

Lead Hostess, 07/2014 to 02/2016

White House - Biloxi, Mississippi

- Greet guest
- Properly seat guest according to server seating chart
- Recorded to go orders and accurately entered into a point of sale system
- Set scheduled party tables up prior to arrival
- Buss tables reset tables
- Use of Point of Sale system
- Catering events setup serve breakdown

Food and Beverage manager, 09/2015 to 08/2016

The Biloxi Lugger - Biloxi, Mississippi

- Daily meeting with Chef to learn specials of the day and items not available on menu
- Upload pictures to our social media page for proper advertising on specials and up coming events
- Designed a daily/weekly section rotational sheet for servers
- Hire/terminations
- Implemented training and retraining when necessary
- Ordered office/bar/front of house inventory and supplies
- Scheduling of employees and live music
- Cash out servers at end of shift and ran reports
- Deposits and kept small denominations in petty cash
- Personally work any position in house if short handed
- Scheduled maintenance
- Did whatever was necessary to run a successful shift